Unterberger, S. Herbert Arbitration and Research Files 5636
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Commonwealth of Pennsylvania (Box 15)
  - Comm. 78-1001, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Comm. 78-1893, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Comm. Swanson, 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Comm. 78-1563, 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Comm. 78-908, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Comm., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Comm. 78-2687, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Comm., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Comm. 78-2689, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Comm. APSCUF, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Comm., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Comm. APSCUF, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Comm. APSCUF, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Comm. 77-93, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Comm. 78-95 etc., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Comm. 78/931, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Comm. 78-711, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Comm. 78-1347, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Comm. 78-1046, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Comm. 78-560, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Comm. 78-148, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Dauphin County - Dorr Oliver Incorporated (Box 16)
  - Davy Powergas, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Davy Powergas, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - DeLaval, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - DeLaval, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - DeLaval, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - DeLaval, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - DeLaval, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - DeLaval, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - DeLaval, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - DeLaval, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Del. Co. Bd. Of Comm., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Del. Co. Times, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Del. Elec. Corp., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Delbar, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Delbar, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Delbar, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Delbar, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Delbar, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Delbar, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Delbar, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Delbar, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - DelBar, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Delbar, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Diamond Family Med. Center, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Disston, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Dorr-Oliver Inc., 1979 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Dorr-Oliver Inc., 1979 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Eastern Firelog Company - Fruehaul (Box 17)
  - Eastern Firelog, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Einstein, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Electric + House (Smith), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Elwyn Institute, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Equity Meat Corp., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Erie Transit, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Exxon Enterprises, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Fabricon, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Fafnir, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Ferguson Propeller, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Fischer + Porter, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Foodarama, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - RCA, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - FMR - Elec. Div., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Fruehauf Corp., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Fruehauf, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Fruehauf, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: George Leno Association - Great Atlantic and Pacific Company (Box 18)
  - George Leno Associates, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Georgia-Pacific Corporation, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - General Time, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Glenco, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Globe Union Inc., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Goodall Rubber Company, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Goodall Rubber, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Goodell Rubber, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Goodell Rubber, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Gorham, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Gould, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Gould Inc., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Gould Inc., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Greer Hydraulics, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Gould Inc., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - A+P, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Robert Hall Company (Box 19)
  - Robert Hall Clothes, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Robert Hall, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Harleco/Dade, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Hunterdon, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Harrisburg Steel Co, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Harrison Color Process, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Hurlock Bros. Company, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - HERCO, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Hershey, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Hillside Cemetery, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Hofman, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Holiday Inn, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Holmdel Police, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Hospital for the Mentally Retarded, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Robert Hall Company - Hospital for the Mentally Retarded (Box 20)
  - IBEW, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - ICI Americas, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Insaco, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Delbar, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - International Silver Co., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - I.T.T. Electron Div., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Jackson Rope Co., 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - John Hancock Mutual Company, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Key Circle Hospice, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Kraft Co., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Kraft (Box 21)
  - Robert Hall, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Robert Hall, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Robert Hall, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - S. Herbert Unterberger, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Employees Hours, Analysis [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Employees Hours, Analysis [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Mr. B. R. Silbert, 1968-1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Lamont Gear - Luzerne County Community College (Box 22)
  - Lamont Gear, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Leeds and Northrup, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Laborers' Dist. Council, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration, 1968-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Leeds and Northrup, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lee and Tire Rubber Company, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Leeds, Northrup, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Leeds + Northrup, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Leeds and Northrup, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Leeds and Northrup, 1960-1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Levitz Furniture, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Luzerne Products, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Luzerne County Community College, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Marlin Rockwell - Muncle Newspapers (Box 23)
  - Marlin Rockwell, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - National Hose Co., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Matthey Bishop, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Medusa, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Metro Wire, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Met. Bd., 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Michael Flynn Inc., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Mahl, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mobil Oil Company, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Mobil Oil Company, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mobil Young, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Mountainside Transport, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Mountainside Board of Education, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Muncie Newspapers Inc., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Montgomery County (Box 23A)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: National Hose Company - Owens-Illinois (Box 24)
  - Naval Facilities, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Navy Dept., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Navy (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Navy - J. Jones, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Navy Yard, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Navy - Arbitrability, 1975-1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - NVF, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Owens - Illinois, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Pacemaker Yacht Company - Pullman, Incorporated (Box 25)
  - Pacemaker Yacht, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Palisades Education Association, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Pinland Container, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - PPL, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - PPL, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Pa. State U., 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Phila. Gear, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Phila. Gear, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Pittsburgh Des Moines, 1964-1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Pittston Hospital, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Playtown, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Polyclinic Hospital, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - -Part of Philadelphia-, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Part of Phila., 1956 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Potlatch Corporation, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - P+W, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Pratt and Whitney, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Progress Lighting, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Trailmobile, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Pennsylvania State College Case (Box 26)
  - Letters Regarding the Selection of Arbitrator for St. Clair School District, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Sentinel Electronics Union Agreement and Copies of Job Classifications for Tinicum and Barker + Williamson, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Agreements Between Pratt & Whitney and Unity Lodge, UAW (1955, 1957, 1959, 1977), 1955-1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Agreement Between Niles-Bement-Pond Co. and Unity Lodge, C.I.O., 1953 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Pratt & Whitney Job Evaluation Plan, 1957-1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney, Award, Case: 12-30-0123-79, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Workers of America vs. Pratt & Whitney, Award, Case: 12-30-0276-77, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Workers of America, Local 4405, Award, Case: 12-30-0055-73 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney, Award for Rating of "Grinder Centerless" Job, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Awards on Grievances 2200-2215, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Award, Case: L-28923 HART-L-185-60, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Award, Case: L-30372 HART-L-66-61, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - IUUAAAIWA, UWA Local 405 vs. Chandler Evans Corporation, Award, Case: L-27936 HART-L-1331-60, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Awards, Grievances 1106-1108, 1145, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Chandler Evans Corporation and Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Awards, Case L-27115 HART-L-42-60, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Letters Regarding the Rules Governing "Technical Arbitrations" at Pratt & Whitney, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Chandler Evans vs. UAW Local 405, Award Regarding Withholding of Incentive Earnings, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Award, Grievance 1026 (June 17), 1959 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney, Awards, Grievances 454, 607, 657, 672 (Dec. 4), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney, Awards, Grievances 20, 607, 620, 622, 623, 819, 823-825, 829, 830, 833-836, 838, 853-855, 884-887, 894, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney and Chandler Evans Corp. Awards, Case: L-23905 HART-L-21-59 (March 27), 1959 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney, Award, Case: L-22242 HART-L-140-58, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Award, Grievance 894 (Sept. 30), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Award, Grievances 884-887 (Oct. 7), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Awards, Grievances 823, 829, 853-855 (April 22), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Awards, Grievances 819, 820, 822 (March 26), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405, Awards, Grievances 823, 824+ (March 1,19), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. Local 405 Awards Grievances 420, 607, 830 ( May 22, June 30), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405 Awards Grievances 833, 834, 836, 838 (May 27), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney Award Case: L-16687 HART-L-83-56, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - UAW Local 405 vs, Pratt & Whitney Award Case L-17072 HART-L-126-56, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405 Award Case L-19096 HART-L-2-56, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - UAW Local 405 vs Pratt & Whitney Awards Cases L-17842 HART-L-188-56, L-17866 HART-L-191-56, L-18456 HART-L-17-57, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney Awards Cases L-18448 HART-L-16-57, L-18447 HART-L-15-57, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Pratt & Whitney Awards Cases L-18695 HART-L-36-57, L-19109 HART-L-87-57, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405 Awards Grievances 454,607,657,627 (Dec 4), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Pratt & Whitney vs. UAW Local 405 Awards Case L-16096 HART-L-2-56 (April 25, 1956) and Grievance 625 ( April 30, 1958), 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - UAW Local 405 vs Pratt & Whitney Awards Case L-16389 HART-L-48-56 (1958), UAW Local 229 vs. Pratt & Whitney Award Case L-16388 HART-L-47-56 (1956), 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - UAW Local 405 vs. Niles Bement Pond Company Award, Case L-14421 HART-L-19-55 And Related Correspondences, 1952-1955 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Association of Penn. State College vs Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol I (Nov 28, 10AM), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Association of Penn. State College vs. Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol II (Nov 28, 1:15PM), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Association of Penn. State College vs. Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol. III (Dec 5, 10AM), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Association of Penn. State College vs. Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol IV (Dec 22, 10AM), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Association of Penn. State College vs. Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol. V (Jan 22, 10AM), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Association of Penn State College vs Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol. VI (Jan 30, 10AM), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Association of Penn State College vs. Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol. VIII (Jan 31, 9AM), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Association of Penn State College vs. Commonwealth of Penn. Verbatim Report of Arbitration Hearing Vol VIII (Feb. 13, 10AM), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Association of Penn State College vs. Commonwealth of Penn. Interim Decisions 1-3, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - College Wide Seniority Lists- Millersville, Bloomsburg, Cheyney, Shippensburg, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Penn Labor Relations Board vs. Commonwealth of Penn. NISI Decision and Order case: PERA-C-6932-C, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Opinions Regarding Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Commonwealth/Colleges and APSCUF on Retrenchment, Article XXVII, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Article XII Professional Development and Evaluation (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Due Process Hearing Procedures (Collective Bargaining Agreement), 1974 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Guidelines for Use in Planning Retrenchment in the State College and University, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Board of State College and University Directors 31st and 32nd Meetings Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Association of Penn State College and Commonwealth of Penn. ( Nov. 2, 1971- Aug. 31, 1971, Sep.1, 1974 onward), 1971- 1974 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Rouse Insurance Agency Seniority List for State College And Seniority List for Retrenched Employees (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Draft Letter to President of State College and University Regarding Budget Appropriations (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Various Rules and Regulations from State College and Indiana University of Penn., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Rules and Statements of Retrenchment, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Transcript of Meeting Between Mr. Raup, Mr. Killian, Dr. Ingster, and Arbitrator, and Witness Regarding Staffing (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Employee Training (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Collective Negotiations in Education, St. Francis College, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Eugene Carroll's Statement to the SCUD Board (Sept.25), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Mansfield State College Deficit Reduction Calculation, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Amendment to Dept. of Education Retirement Resolution Approved 08-30-74, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Summary and Guidelines Regarding Promotion Policies and Practices, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - News Releases, clippings, and Press Conference Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Memorandum from the State College and Indiana University Negotiating Team, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Arbitration/Judicial Process Form (Blank), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Statement of Mutual Understanding and Miscellaneous Papers Regarding State College Rules, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Letters Between Parties Regarding Arbitration over Retrenchment (March 26, 1975- March 23, 1976), 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Clerical Study by Governor's Office of Administration, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 73)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Puerto Rico Industry and Trade Association Case (Box 27)
  - ALPA Mutual Aid, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Kayser-Roth Corporation, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Brackets, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - The Shoe and Related Products Industry of Puerto Rico, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Production Data, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Puerto Rico Bx 27, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Puerto Rico Industry and Trade Association Case (Box 28)
  - Wages and Hours, 1955-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Wages and Hours Division, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 1975 Prehearing Statement on Behalf of: Caravelle, Inc. Embroidery Management Corp. Maribet Manufacturing Corp. Palm Undies, Inc. Soft-Knit Undies, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 1973 Prehearing Statement (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - The Glove and Mittens Industry, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico, 1965-1969 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 1976 Prehearing Statement on Behalf of: Caravelle, Inc., Embroidery Management Corp. Palm Undies Soft-Knit Undies, Inc. Ronmar, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Puerto Rico Industry and Trade Association Case (Box 29)
  - Wage and Hour Division U.S. Department of Labor, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Handkerchief, Scarf and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - The Rubber Products Industry in Puerto Rico, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Clothing Industries of Puerto Rico, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Clothing - Puerto Rico, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Balance Sheets - Nonrubber Footwear Industry of Puerto Rico, 1948-1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Puerto Rico Industry and Trade Association Case (Box 30)
  - Gloves, 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - The Manufacture of Women's and Children's Underwear in the 50 States, 1958-1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - The Fabric and Leather Glove Industry in Puerto Rico, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Wages - Puerto Rico, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Apparel Co. - Puerto Rico, 1963-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Handkerchief, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Puerto Rico Industry and Trade Association Case (Box 31)
  - Clothing Industry Puerto Rico, 1963-1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - A And J Industries, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - The Apparel Industry in Puerto Rico, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Wage and Hour Division, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Employment Data, 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Puerto Rico Industry and Trade Association Case (Box 32)
  - Wage and Hour Division U.S. Department of Labor, 1962-1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Puerto Rico - Wage and Hour Division, 1962-1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Bound, Spanish
  - Shoes - 1974 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Wages and Hours Puerto Rico, 1959-1963 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Handkerchief (?) No Longer in Business, 1962-1965 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Guaranteed Wage -and- Supplementary Unemployment Pay Plans, 1962-1974 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Anasco Sports Co. Inc., 1964 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Handkerchief Economic Report Carbon Copy No. 3, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Quoka Oats, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - RCA, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Quaker Oats - Rose Tree Meadai School District (Box 33)
  - RCA, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - RCA, 1974-1979 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - RCA, 1976-1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - RCA, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - RCA, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Reconditioned Motor and Parts Co., 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Resorts International, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Piper Aircraft Job Evaluations, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Rite Aid Corporation, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Rose Tree Media Education Association, 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Saint Clair Area School District - Superior Tube Company (Box 34)
  - Saint Joseph Hospital, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - St. Joseph Hospital, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - School Dist. Of Philadelphia, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - School Dist., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - School Dist., 1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - School District, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Scott Paper Company, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ship N' Bag, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Slaymaker Lock Co., 1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - SEPTA, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - South Jersey Gas Company, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Seed Co., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - The Stanley Works, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Stanley Works, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Simson, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Stauffer, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Stylex, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Marcus Hook Refinery, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Sun Petroleum, 1970-1978 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Sun Petroleum, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Superior Dental, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Superior Motors, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Superior Tube, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Tally-Ho Motor Lodge - Victor Balata Belting Company (Box 35)
  - Tally Ho, 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Temple, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Temple, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Temple, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Texaco, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Texaco, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Texaco, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Tuscan Dairy Farms, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Industrial Chemicals Co., 1979 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Industrial Chemicals, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - United News Transportation Company, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Upholsterers', 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Victor Balata, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - York Water, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Wallerstein Company (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Victor Balata, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Wallerstein Company - Yarway Corporation (Box 36)
  - Walterstein Company, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Warner-Lambert, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Westinghouse, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Western Kraft Paper Group, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "The Whetzel Case" West Penn Power Company Arbitration, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "The Linc Case" West Penn Power Co. UWUA, AFL-CIO Arbitration, 1956-1973 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - WF Trucking Co., 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Weyerhauser Company, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - White Motor Company, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Winkersham Printing Company, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Wilkes-Barre, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Whiting Patterson, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 12)